Guide to the Jennie Farley papers, 1969-1980.
Farley, Jennie papers, 1969-1980.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jennie Farley papers, 1969-1980.
25-3-2710
Jennie Farley.
3 c.f.
Papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers pertaining to the Women's Studies Program, the Provost's Committee on Women, the Trustees Committee on the Status of Women, the Women's Studies Friday Seminars, the Professional Skills Roster, and other issues.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Papers pertaining to the Women's Studies Program, the Provost's Committee on Women, the Trustees Committee on the Status of Women, the Women's Studies Friday Seminars, the Professional Skills Roster, and other issues.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Farley, Jennie.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees. Committee on the Status of Women.; Cornell University. Provost's Committee on Women.; Cornell University. Women's Studies Program.; Professional Skills Roster.
Subjects:
Women college teachers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Kram Award (Box 1)
- Women's Studies Graduate Minor, 1978- (Box 1)
- Women's Studies Minor - 1, 2, 3 (Box 1)
- Works in Progress: Continuing Education - 1, 1974- (Box 1)
- Provost's Advisory Committee on Women, 1973- (Box 1)
- Committees: Trustee Committee on Status of Women, 1972- (Box 1)
- Friday Seminars - New York State Council Proposal (Box 2)
- Women's Studies Friday Seminars
  - Fall 1976 (Box 2)
  - Spring 1977 (Box 2)
  - Fall 1977 (Box 2)
  - Spring 1978 (Box 2)
  - Fall 1978 (Box 2)
  - Spring 1979 (Box 2)
  - Fall 1979 (Box 2)
  - Spring 1980 (Box 2)
- Professional Skills Roster (Box 3)
- Evaluation of Professional Skills Roster (Box 3)
- Jobs: Running List of Jobs and Matches, 1969 to present (Box 3)
- Women's Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 3)